Found you! Good morning, Python brothers! Welcome to "Python's First POV". Dear owners,
Have a small bench ready. The old rules, the python game, should be avoided by netizen players for the time being. It is only suitable for entertaining squatters.
I made my debut with a double-barreled spray gun, a steel helmet, and a few meters of spaceflight. In this game, we were born in the second position.
After we get up to this position, we first check to see if there is any oil. Just inside this original color jar,
And the yellow storage box on the left will also be brushed. If there are none, let’s just move in and add another hand.
See if the opponent wants to go up the suspension bridge, or come from the left. After seeing that there was no movement on the suspension bridge,
I thought that the third child didn't swipe anyone, but I found that the suspension bridge was open.
Then let's just block the opposite way with two electric swords, and at the same time call our teammates to come over quickly.
After all, our first-hand handling of Ma Xiarong is still relatively low. Here we have another small room,
Avoid the opponent's direct counterattack. After there was no movement, two grenades were fired to seal the road forward. Then let's continue to change points,
Find cover ahead. We happened to encounter a machine gunner on the opposite side, so we moved in and fired two shots first.
But there is a bit of a carbine here, so it’s not a big problem. After driving in again, I found that the carbine was fired again.
That forces us.
You can only turn on fire control and use the preview point to judge the opponent's position. After the fire control here is turned on,
He didn't fall down even after two shots. He looks strong! But can you take another shot? After clicking one,
At the same time, his teammates also won the next one. Then three against one,
We can move forward boldly and confidently. If we see the other side grabbing our teammates, let’s change our bullets.
Directly open the camera and take away the team, successfully destroying the team. But us.
You are suspicious by nature! Maybe I wasn't shooting machine gunners just now.
So let’s not follow our teammates and rush forward so fast. Sure enough, one of his teammates fell first,
Then let's suppress the opponent with thunder, and then quickly find cover behind us. Two teammates fell here.
Since there was only one type of gunshot just now, it can be concluded that there was basically only one person. The ultimate move is now cooled down.
Just use a detection arrow to find the opponent's position and kill him with two shots. This is the power of the Blind Man.
Just after rescuing his teammates here, he found footsteps on the first floor. Found a lone wolf uncle,
Then we also drive into the nursery. There is no need for fire control at close range, and we can directly take it away with two rounds.
I have to be a fool to be entertaining! So this wave can be considered as killing four people.
Let’s take a look at what supplies are available. It's so strange, why is his armor broken?
A lousy warrior with an unattractive helmet. Come and take a look inside the bag, wow,
There is also a satellite pot, this wave.
The harvest is fat, fat. As a result, after we collected the supplies, we found that our teammates had jumped into the water to evacuate and drowned directly.
There is no other way to escape by diving. We can only go to the black market first. After exploring all the way,
We came to the president's position. If we see an enemy with its head tilted, let's suppress it with a grenade.
Then the blind man raised the seedlings. After there was no movement, he directly cut the gun and pressed forward. It was a person who got the information,
Then am I still afraid?
What are you afraid of? Hey, no, why are there suddenly a squatting dog and an Uluru? OK
Dear owners, do you think I can win this round? Hey, he thinks I can win. Why,
I think I can win too. Okay, then this is over.